industrywest.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy

Industry West's Privacy Policy ("Policy") sets out what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it. Please contact us at 

1538-2 Hendricks Ave  
Jacksonville, FL 32207

or by phone at 800.382.9303 or via email at [info@industrywest.com](mailto:info@industrywest.com) if you have any questions or would like additional information regarding this Policy. We may update this Policy from time to time, so please check this Policy periodically for changes.

#### YOUR INFORMATION

As a online-based furniture design, production and wholesale store, we may collect non-public, personal information directly from our customers, including when our customers place orders through our online stores located at www.industrywest.com. We define "personal information" as information that is unique to an individual and might include the following: name, contact and billing information, email addresses, and telephone numbers. We will update your information whenever we can to keep it current, accurate and complete.

#### OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

If we do receive your personal information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected, and we will not sell, license, transmit or disclose this information outside of Industry West unless (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to allow our service providers or agents to provide services for us, (3) in order to provide our services to you (and contacting you when necessary), (4) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is disclosed to entities that perform marketing services on our behalf or to other entities with whom we have joint marketing agreements, (5) subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, it is necessary in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Industry West or the merger of Industry West into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Industry West is not the survivor, (6) it is necessary in connection with other business purposes including, without limitation, customer care, service quality, business management and operation, risk assessment, security, fraud and crime prevention/detection, monitoring, research and analysis, marketing, customer purchasing preferences and trends, dispute resolution, credit checking and debt collection, or (7) otherwise as we are required or permitted by law.

If you are a California resident, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your personal information (whether collected online or offline) with third parties for their marketing purposes. Please tell us your preference by contacting us as indicated in the "How to Contact Us" section of this Policy.

If you do not agree to Our Use of Your Information above, we cannot do business with you or accept online orders for products or services. Your continued use of our web site, or purchase of products or services constitutes your acceptance of this Policy.

#### CONTESTS, SWEEPSTAKES AND OTHER PROMOTIONS

On our web site, you may wish to participate in contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time. Through these promotions, you may choose to participate in activities such as sharing information found on our web site with others and sending email invitations. If you choose to participate in these promotions, and are eligible to do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, date of birth and telephone number.

In connection with any contests, sweepstakes and other promotions that we may offer from time to time via the web site, we use the information you provide to administer the contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we also may use the information to communicate with you, or the other people you select, about our products and services or our partners may use such information to communicate with you about the contests, sweepstakes or other promotions or their products and services. In connection with such contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, we will not use information you provide about other people for any purpose except the purpose you direct without first getting their consent.

#### DIRECT MARKETING MATERIAL

Subject to applicable contractual or legal restrictions, we may from time to time contact you with information on offers of goods and services, brochures, new products, forthcoming events. Our web site will assume you to agree to electronic communications when you make a purchase or request services online. You may indicate your preference regarding receiving third party direct marketing material. If do not wish to receive such information or would like to change your preference, please refer to "Your Rights" below.

#### EMAIL

We appreciate your questions and comments about Industry West and its products and services and welcome your email messages to [info@industrywest.com](mailto:info@industrywest.com). We will share your messages with those within our organization who are most capable of addressing the issues contained in your message. We will keep a copy of your message until we have had an opportunity to address your concerns. We may archive your message for a certain period of time or discard it once it is no longer needed.

#### YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask in writing not to receive direct marketing material from us. If available, you can amend your previous preference by emailing **"unsubscribe email"** to [info@industrywest.com](mailto:info@industrywest.com) or refer to our literature containing instructions. Once properly notified by you, we will take steps to stop using your information in this way. Please allow us a reasonable period of time in order to satisfy your request.

#### USE OF TOOLS, "COOKIES" AND LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

If our contact and dealing with you is via our web site(s), we may use "cookies". Cookies allow us to identify your computer, but not you personally. You can set your web browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to enjoy access and use all of the services available to you on our web site.

However, if you also receive our email marketing, we will tailor the information we send you unless you to tell us not to. This means we may use information we hold and cookies to identify your individual web site search behavior and preferences. This will enable us to send you more personalized and relevant communications. You will be given the opportunity on every communication to opt-out of this personalization.

We collect information relating to customer trends and patterns and use cookies and software tools to measure site usage and related information. If you are making a purchase, we may also use cookies to keep track of the transaction from one web page to another.

In addition to the information we collect from cookies, we also obtain information which you provide to us online - for example, when you sign up for service updates or when you purchase products or otherwise communicate with us. In some cases, we retain both the cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online - for example, to complete a transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases, we only retain the cookie and/or online information you give us if you request us to do so for your use in subsequent sessions.

An Internet Protocol ("IP") address is a unique identifier that certain electronic devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. When you visit our web site, we may view the IP address (which may include the city, domain address and service provider) of the device you use to connect to the Internet. We use this information to determine the general physical location of the device and understand from what regions of the world our web site visitors come. We also may use this information to enhance our web site.

Certain pages on our web site contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

#### CHILDREN

We are committed to preserving online privacy for all of the visitors to our web site, including children. Our web site is a general audience web site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children or provide services to children. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. The Industry West web site is not designed to attract anyone under the age of 18. In certain instances, we may sell children's products for purchase by adults.

#### MONITORING

To ensure that we carry out your instructions accurately, improve our products, services and for security, we may monitor and/or record: (1) telephone calls; (2) activities using CCTV in and around our premises; and (3) transactions and activities on our web site. All recordings are and shall remain our sole property.

#### SECURITY STATEMENT

We have taken all reasonable steps and have in place appropriate security measures to protect your personal information, including keeping your financial information private and safe. If you make purchases on our web site we will ask for credit card information, but we do not store the information after the secure transaction is complete. You acknowledge, however, that no transmission of data over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, despite our best efforts. Thus, while we will use every means possible to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties.

#### VISITING OUR WEB SITE FROM OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES

If you are visiting our web site or purchasing our products from outside of the United States or otherwise contacting us from outside of the United States, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored or processed in the United States, where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country, but please be assured that we take steps to protect your privacy. By using our services or purchasing our products, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Policy.

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We may change this Policy at any time and from time to time. Any changes to this Policy will be either posted on our web site, brochure and/or made available on request. The most recent version of the Policy is reflected by the version date located at the bottom of this Policy. This Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

#### LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES

For your convenience, we may provide links to other web sites and web pages that we do not control. We cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of any web sites or pages not under our control and we do not endorse any of these web sites or pages, the services or products described or offered on such sites or pages, or any of the content contained on those sites or pages.

#### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Policy or would like to learn more about how we protect privacy, please write to us at Industry West, 4011 Morton Street, Jacksonville, FL, 32217 or call us at 800.382.9303, or email us at [info@industrywest.com](mailto:info@industrywest.com)

Privacy Policy: last updated June 4, 2012.
